Guide to the Polly Shackleton papers, 1894-1997 MS2031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Office files, 1968-1986; Series 9
  - Office files I-P, 1968-1986; Series 9 Subseries 3
    - Invitations (11 of 16), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Invitations (12 of 16), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Invitations (13 of 16), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Invitations (14 of 16), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Invitations (15 of 16), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (16 of 16), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Invitations (1 of 4), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Invitations (2 of 4), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Invitations (3 of 4), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (4 of 4), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Journal of Northeast Asian Studies, 1987-1989; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - JUD Budget Mark Up (1 of 3), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - JUD Budget Mark Up (2 of 3), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - JUD Budget Mark Up (3 of 3), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - JUD Hearing, 1984 February 22; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - JUD Hearing (1 of 8), 1984 February 22; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - JUD Hearing (2 of 8), 1984 February 22; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - JUD Hearing (3 of 8), 1984 February 22; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - JUD Hearing (4 of 8), 1984 February 22; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - JUD Hearing (5 of 8), 1984 February 22; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - JUD Hearing (6 of 8), 1984 February 22; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - JUD Hearing (7 of 8), 1984 February 22; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - JUD Hearing (8 of 8), 1984 February 22; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - JUD Hearing (Metro Police), 1984 February 15; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - JUD Hearing Mark Up (1 of 7), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - JUD Hearing Mark Up (2 of 7), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - JUD Hearing Mark Up (3 of 7), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - JUD Hearing Mark Up (4 of 7), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - JUD Hearing Mark Up (5 of 7), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - JUD Hearing Mark Up (6 of 7), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - JUD Hearing Mark Up (7 of 7), 1984 February 25; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Junior League, 1980-1981; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Laws - Elections & Boundries, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - League of Women Voters, 1976-1977; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Legislative History - Boundries and Elections, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Legislative History - Duties, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Letters and statements, 1962-1963; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Letters etc., 1961-1963; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Letters of Consituents Opposing Raising the Drinking Age, 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Licenses and Inspections, 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Lobby - School Board Budget, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Location of Chanceries, 1974-1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Location of Chanceries I, 1981-1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Location of Chanceries II, 1978-1980; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - LYRA Budget/Mark Up, 1984 February 27; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - LYRA Hearing (1 of 2), 1984 February 10; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - LYRA Hearing (2 of 2), 1984 February 10; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Martin Luther King Jr., 1968-1970; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Mathadone, 1969; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Mayor, 1975-1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Mayor, 1974-1975; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Mayor (1 of 11), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Mayor (2 of 11), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Mayor (3 of 11), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Mayor (4 of 11), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Mayor (5 of 11), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Mayor (6 of 11), 1979-1983; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Mayor (7 of 11), 1982-1983; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Mayor (8 of 11), 1983; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Mayor (9 of 11), 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Mayor (10 of 11), 1981; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Mayor (11 of 11), 1981; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Mayor's Task Force on Public Health, 1969; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Meetings, 1970; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Memoranda-Council Calendar, 1978; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Memos to/from Director Department of Human Resources, 1977; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Memos to/from Director Department of Human Resources, 1976; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Memos to/from Director Department of Human Resources, 1978; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Memos/New Releases, 1977; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Metro, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Misc., 1967-1970; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous - Memoranda, Act, Fiscal Year Financial Plan Assambly for a Better Community, Anacostia Community Directory, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous re-election info, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Model Cities, 1963-1968; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - More re-election propoganda, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1981-1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1981-1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1981; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1981; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - New Clippings, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - News clips, 1962; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - No-Fault (State Farm) Geico, 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - No-Fault Press Clips and News Releases, 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - No-Fault Referendum, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - No-Fault-HALT Correspondence & Proposals (1 of 2), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - No-Fault-HALT Correspondence & Proposals (2 of 2), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - No-Fault-Hearing (1 of 3), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - No-Fault-Hearing (2 of 3), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - No-Fault-Hearing (3 of 3), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - No-Fault-Legislation Sessions (1 of 3), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - No-Fault-Legislation Sessions (2 of 3), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - No-Fault-Legislation Sessions (3 of 3), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - No-Fault-Letters Against, 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - No-Fault-Letters of Support Individual & Organizations (1 of 5), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - No-Fault-Letters of Support Individual & Organizations (2 of 5), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - No-Fault-Letters of Support Individual & Organizations (3 of 5), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - No-Fault-Letters of Support Individual & Organizations (4 of 5), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - No-Fault-Letters of Support Individual & Organizations (5 of 5), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - No-Fault-Mark-Up-Committee on CRA, 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - No-Fault-Statements-P.S., 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - No-Fault-Studies, etc (U.S. D.O.T. - Court Cases)(1 of 4), 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - No-Fault-Studies, etc (U.S. D.O.T. - Court Cases)(2 of 4), Undated; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - No-Fault-Studies, etc (U.S. D.O.T. - Court Cases)(3 of 4), 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - No-Fault-Studies, etc (U.S. D.O.T. - Court Cases)(4 of 4), Undated; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Notes of Opposition to ABC Amendment, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Office and Campaign Finance - General, 1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Office of Aging, 1975-1978; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Office of Business & Executive Development, 1908; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Office of Campaign Finance, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Office of Human Rights, 1975-1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Office of Human Rights, 1979-1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Office of Intergovernmental Relations, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Office of Latino Affairs, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Office of Personel, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Office of the Executive Secretary, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Office of the Executive Secretary, 1980; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Oldest Inhabitants Inc., 1968; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Opposition Cards, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Opposition Cards, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Opposition Letters, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Opposition Letters, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Opposition Letters to Raising the Drinking Age, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - P.S. Re-election propaganda, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Parking Sticker Program Ward 3 (1 of 3), 1978-1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Parking Sticker Program Ward 3 (2 of 3), 1977-1978; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Parking Sticker Program Ward 3 (3 of 3), 1976; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Photographs - Defense Housing Project, Center Line Michigan, n.d., undated; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Plan a Month, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Plan a Month, 1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Plan a Month, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Planners, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Plunket Heir, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1981; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1983; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1976; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1977; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1978; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Pocket Dayminder, 1980; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Police - Community Relations, 1969; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Police DC, 1975-1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Police Regs on Secondhand Clothing - Junior League, 1980-1981; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Political Action Committee, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Post Election, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Potomac Boat Club, 1969; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Pre-School Program Syphax Housing Project, 1968; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Prohibition of Discrimination in the Provision of Insurance, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Property Tax (1 of 3), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Property Tax (2 of 3), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Property Tax (3 of 3), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Property Tax (1 of 7), 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Property Tax (2 of 7), 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Property Tax (3 of 7), 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Property Tax (4 of 7), 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Property Tax (5 of 7), 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Property Tax (6 of 7), 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Property Tax (7 of 7), 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Property Tax (1 of 3), 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Property Tax (2 of 3), 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Property Tax (3 of 3), 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Property Tax Problems (1 of 7), 1981-1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Property Tax Problems (2 of 7), 1981-1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Property Tax Problems (3 of 7), 1981-1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Property Tax Problems (4 of 7), 1981-1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Property Tax Problems (5 of 7), 1981-1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Property Tax Problems (6 of 7), 1981-1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Property Tax Problems (7 of 7), 1981-1985; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Proposals for Election Reform, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - PSCT Budget/Mark Up, 1984 February 14; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - PSCT Hearing (1 of 3), 1984 February 08; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - PSCT Hearing (2 of 3), 1984 February 08; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - PSCT Hearing (3 of 3), 1984 February 08; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Public Hearing on Budget for the Dept of Finance and Revenue, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Public Schools, 1966-1968; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Public Works, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Publications, 1974-1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Publications, 1977-1981; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Publications, 1976-1982; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Office files R-Y, 1968-1986; Series 9 Subseries 4
    - R Personal Property Tax (1 of 4), 1978-1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - R Personal Property Tax (2 of 4), 1978-1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - R Personal Property Tax (3 of 4), 1978-1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - R Personal Property Tax (4 of 4), 1978-1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Re-election paraphernalia, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Re-election receipts, 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Reconstruction Development Corp., 1968-1970; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Reconstruction Development Corp. Ford Foundation Grant, 1970; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Recreation Department, 1967-1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Red Line Opening, 1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Regular Meeting Committee on the Judiciary, 1981; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Relection Committee - Binder, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Relection Committee - Binder 2, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Remarks (1 of 5), Undated; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Remarks (2 of 5), 1966-1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Remarks (3 of 5), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Remarks (4 of 5), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Remarks (5 of 5), 1970; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Reno Road (1 of 7), 1981-1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Reno Road (2 of 7), 1980-1981; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Reno Road (3 of 7), 1980-1982; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Reno Road (4 of 7), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Reno Road (5 of 7), 1982; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Reno Road (6 of 7), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Reno Road (7 of 7), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Rent Control, 1983; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Reports (1), 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Reports (2), 1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Reprogramming, 1981; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Reprogrammings, 1980-1983; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Resource Recovery, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Resource Recovery, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Resumes, 1982-1986; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Resumes, 1978-1980; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Resumes, 1976-1977; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Resumes, 1975-1976; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Retirement Board, 1983-1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Revenue Source Funding, 1979; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Sanitary Engineering (1 of 2), 1968-1970; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Sanitary Engineering (2 of 2), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Schedule, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Scheduling, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - School Board Budget 1, 1980-1982; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - School Board Budget 2, 1980-1982; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - School Board Election, 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - School Leasing Authority Ed. Licensure, 1982; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Secretary to the Council (1 of 9), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Secretary to the Council (2 of 2), 1982; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Secretary to the Council (2 of 9), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Secretary to the Council (3 of 9), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Secretary to the Council (4 of 9), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Secretary to the Council (5 of 9), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Secretary to the Council (6 of 9), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Secretary to the Council (7 of 9), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Secretary to the Council (8 of 9), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Secretary to the Council (9 of 9), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Senate Documents Bound Volume, A System of Civil and Criminal Law for the District of Columbia, 1833; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Senior Citizens (1 of 2), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Senior Citizens (2 of 2), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Shackleton Nameplate, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Shackleton Signature Stamp, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Shackleton, Polly (1 of 7), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Shackleton, Polly (2 of 7), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Shackleton, Polly (3 of 7), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Shackleton, Polly (4 of 7), 1968-1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Shackleton, Polly (5 of 7), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Shackleton, Polly (6 of 7), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Shackleton, Polly (7 of 7), 1968; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Shackleton, Polly Councilwoman (1 of 3), 1970; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Shackleton, Polly Councilwoman (2 of 3), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Shackleton, Polly Councilwoman (3 of 3), 1970; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (1 of 10), 1979-1981; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (2 of 10), 1980-1984; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (3 of 10), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (4 of 10), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (5 of 10), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (6 of 10), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (7 of 10), 1980; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (8 of 10), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (9 of 10), 1979; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Sheraton Park Hotel (10 of 10), 1978; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Sidwell Friends School, 1979-1983; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Southern District - Consumer Affairs Hearing, 1968; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Southern District (1 of 5), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Southern District (2 of 5), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Southern District (3 of 5), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Southern District (4 of 5), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Southern District (5 of 5), 1969; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Spanish Speaking Community (1 of 2), 1970; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Spanish Speaking Community (2 of 2), 1970; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Speech material and Kennedy documents, 1962; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Speeches-speech material, 1962-1963; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Spring Valley Traffic, 1975; Series 9 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 1)